

Dawid Zabrzeński



577 039 781



dawidzabrzenski00@gmail.com



dzabrzenski.pl

I'm a 24-year-old Frontend Developer with 2 years of experience in designing and implementing user-friendly web interfaces. I specialize in JavaScript, React, and Next.js, focusing on creating responsive and visually appealing websites. I have experience working with modern front-end technologies, state management, and performance optimization. Additionally, I have a basic understanding of backend technologies like Node.js/Express and databases (MongoDB with Mongoose, PostgreSQL).

Work Experience

GF Corp

Front End Developer

2024 - present

- Creating web and user-friendly solutions for managing the ERP system (React + Node.js + MongoDB)
- Implementing SEO improvements and fixes to meet audit requirements.
- Managing CMS e-commerce system (IdoSell and Wordpress)

UNIVERSAL SCIENTIFIC INDUSTRIAL POLAND

2023 - 2024

Junior MES System Developer

- Maintenance and development of web applications related to production system based on Oracle DB
- Basic development of applications in .NET and Java

Skills

- · Building responsive pages using HTML, CSS/Sass/Tailwind/CSS Modules, JavaScript and React.
- · Knowledge and experience in working with most of the React hooks
- Skilled in designing and implementing custom React hooks to encapsulate reusable logic
- Managing the global state of app with Context API/Redux.
- Proficiency in TypeScript, leveraging its static typing to catch potential bugs early in the development process.
- · Experienced in using React Query to manage serverside state efficiently, enabling seamless data fetching, caching, synchronization, and updating of data in React applications.

Skills

- React
- Next.js
- Redux, React Query
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Node.js, Express
- Tailwind, Sass, Less
- · Docker, Git
- Figma

Languages

- polish native
- english B2

Education

Wrocławska Wyższa Szkoła Informatyki Stosowanej

Engineer - Computer Science 2020-2024

Specialization: Programming